Faculty Reference Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
Faculty Reference Collection1845-present
nam_ua950.003
Reference file of former and current UAlbany faculty members.
University at Albany Foundation
42.25 cubic ft.
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
Biographical History
The University at Albany has a long history dating back to 1844 when it was established as the New York State Normal School to train teachers. The faculty have always played a major role in the school though its time as a small state liberal arts college and its evolution into a major public research institution.
This collection was originally a file created and used by the UAlbany Foundation, a nonprofit fundraising corporation for the University at Albany, SUNY. The "faculty file" was transferred to the University Archives where is serves as a general reference source for former and current faculty members.
File contain news articles, clippings, faculty curriculum vitae (CV), and other promotional or public relations material. This collection does not contain any personnel records or private information.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection has no series, organized alphabetically by last name.
Acquisition Information
The vast majority items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by the University at Albany Foundation.
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Subject and Genre Headings
University at Albany Foundation.; State University of New York at Albany.; Faculty (Education); public relations; clippings (information artifacts); promotional documents
Container List
- Aarnio, Johan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abdo, Baaklini - Director of the Center for Legislative Development, Public Affairs and Policy (1972-1990) (1990-2003), nam_ua950.003-2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abelson, Laurie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Able, Kenneth - Biology Department, Undated; nam_ua950.003-4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Abrams, Jay H. (1971-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Abraham, J. Philippe, Undated; nam_ua950.003-6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Abramson, Julie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Aceto, Vincent John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Acker, James R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Acosta- Belen, Edna, Undated; nam_ua950.003-10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Adams, Harold W. - Department of Public Affairs (1966-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Adams, Harriet, Undated; nam_ua950.003-12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Adams, Theodore S. (1959-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Addotta, Antionette E. - Librarian, University Libraries (1980-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Affinito, Stephanie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agee, Jane Murray, Undated; nam_ua950.003-16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agrawal, Rajendra K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Aguilar, Edwin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Aguirre- Ghiso, Julio, Undated; nam_ua950.003-19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ahmad, Shamshad, Undated; nam_ua950.003-20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Aken, Rita - Hispanic and Italian Studies (1981-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Akullian, Agnes - College Nursing Services, Undated; nam_ua950.003-22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Alam, Mohammad S. - Department of Physics (1984-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Alba, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Albagli, Richard - Music Department Composer-Percusionist (1974-) (1942-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Albano, Dr. Anne Marie - Center for Stress and Anxiety Disorders, Undated; nam_ua950.003-26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Aldrich, Margaret H. - Assistant Director Student Activities (1981-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Alexander II, Douglas - French, Undated; nam_ua950.003-28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Alexander, Franklin - Art Department, Undated; nam_ua950.003-29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Alexander, John W. - Placement Offices (1977-1984), Undated; nam_ua950.003-30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Aliotti, Nicholas C. - School of Education (1970-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Allaud, Guy D. - Department of Mathematics (1968,1969-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Allard, Wilfred P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Allen, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Allen, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Allen, Laurel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Allen, Richard L. - Department of Rhetoric and Communications (1978-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Allen, Wayne - Physical Plant, Undated; nam_ua950.003-38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Alliger, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Allington, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Alonso, Damaso - Spanish Department, Undated; nam_ua950.003-41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Alonso-Regalado, Jesus - History Subject Librarian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Alrutz, Daniel J. - Plant Department (1977-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Altrock, Barbara, Undated; nam_ua950.003-44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Altarriba, Jeanette, Undated; nam_ua950.003-45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Alvar, Manuel - Hispanic and Italian Studies (1988-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Alvord, Gregory, Undated; nam_ua950.003-47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Ambach, Gordon M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-48 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Anastasiow, Mary A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-49 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Anderson, Carl, Undated; nam_ua950.003-50 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Anderson, Carol L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-51 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Andersen, David F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-52 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Andersen, Deborah Lines, Undated; nam_ua950.003-53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Andersen, Robert Niels, Undated; nam_ua950.003-54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Anderson, Drew A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Anderson Francis H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-56 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Anderson, James A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-57 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Anderson, Janet, Undated; nam_ua950.003-58 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Anderson, Thomas C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-59 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Andrasik, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-60 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Andrea, Robert K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-61 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Andrews, Linda O., Undated; nam_ua950.003-62 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Andreyewsky, Alexander, Undated; nam_ua950.003-63 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Angus, Johnnie Gillespie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-64 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Angelis, Janet, Undated; nam_ua950.003-65 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Angell, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-66 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Anolik, Boris, Undated; nam_ua950.003-67 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Applebum, Hannah B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-68 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Applebee, Arthur, Undated; nam_ua950.003-69 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Applegate, Mary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-70 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Arana- Downs, Ruben, Undated; nam_ua950.003-71 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Arbitman, Idal, Undated; nam_ua950.003-72 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Archambeault, Deborah, Undated; nam_ua950.003-73 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Archer, Jeffrey - Business Bibliographer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-74 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Arden, Dean N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-75 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Arensberg, Mary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-76 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Armlin, Nelson J. - CASDA (1977-), Undated; nam_ua950.003-77 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Armour-Garb, Brad, Undated; nam_ua950.003-78 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Donna, Undated; nam_ua950.003-79 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Armstrong, Roberta, Undated; nam_ua950.003-80 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Armstrong, Ronald E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-81 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Arnason, Geirmunder, Undated; nam_ua950.003-82 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Arnason, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-83 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arnold, Donald F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-84 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Aronson, John Noel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-85 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Arterburn, Alfred B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-86 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Asermely, Albert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-87 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Ashberry, John N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-88 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Astiz, Carlos, Undated; nam_ua950.003-89 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Atiya, Snmer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-90 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Atkinson, Steven D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-91 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Auclair, Jean-Louis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-92 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Auclair, Lois Gregg, Undated; nam_ua950.003-93 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- August, Debra J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-94 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Auricchio, Pasquale (Pat), Undated; nam_ua950.003-95 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Austin, Bill, Undated; nam_ua950.003-96 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Austin, Sandra, Undated; nam_ua950.003-97 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Avant, Deborah, Undated; nam_ua950.003-98 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Averyt, Bennet, Undated; nam_ua950.003-99 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Avisar, Ilan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-100 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Axelrod, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-101 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Baaklini, Abdo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-102 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Bacher, Frank Jr., 1997; nam_ua950.003-103 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Baer, Judith A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-104 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Baglioni, Corrado, Undated; nam_ua950.003-105 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Bailey, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-106 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Bailey, Elaine M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-107 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Bailey, Frankie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-108 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Bakhru, Hassaram, Undated; nam_ua950.003-109 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Balaban, Miriam, Undated; nam_ua950.003-110 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Baldwin, Alexinia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-111 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Baldwin, Alexinia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-112 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Balk, Walter L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-113 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Balk, Walter L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-114 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Ballard, Allen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-115 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Ballou, Donald P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-116 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Ban, Carolyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-117 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Bank, Shelton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-118 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Baran, Henryk, Undated; nam_ua950.003-119 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Barker, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-120 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Barker-Benfield, Graham J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-121 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Barker-Flynn, Holly, Undated; nam_ua950.003-122 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Barlau, Stephen B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-123 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Barlow, David H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-124 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Barnard, Stephen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-125 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Barnard, Sylvia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-126 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Barnes-Ostrander, Marilyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-127 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Barnett, Thomas R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-128 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Barone, Sandro A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-129 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Barreto, Ernesto, Undated; nam_ua950.003-130 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Barry, David G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-131 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Barry, J.K.M., 1917; nam_ua950.003-132 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Barth, Michael E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-133 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Bartow, Jonathan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-134 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Bashkoff, Jacueline, Undated; nam_ua950.003-135 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Bass, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-136 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Bates, Pamela A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-137 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Baum, Maude, Undated; nam_ua950.003-138 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Baum, Rachel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-139 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Baum, Werner C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-140 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Bayer, Theodore J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-141 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Baxley, DiAnn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-142 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Beauchamp, Dan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-143 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bechet, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-144 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Beck, Thomas D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-145 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Becker, Wendy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-146 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Bedian, Judy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-147 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Beditz, Steve, Undated; nam_ua950.003-148 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Beeten, Scott, Undated; nam_ua950.003-149 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Begam, Ann G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-150 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Begg, Nancy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-151 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Begley, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-152 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Beharriell, Frederick J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-153 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Beckhard, Mozaffar, Undated; nam_ua950.003-154 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Belanger, Michele, Undated; nam_ua950.003-155 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Belardo, Salvatore, Undated; nam_ua950.003-156 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Belasen, Alan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-157 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Belding, S.B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-158 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Belfort, Marlene, Undated; nam_ua950.003-159 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bell, Robert, 1954-1966; nam_ua950.003-160 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Belowich-Negron, Nancy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-161 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Benade, Arthur, Undated; nam_ua950.003-162 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Benedict, Marjorie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-163 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Benedict, Peter C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-164 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Benenson, Raymond E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-165 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Benezet, Louis T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-166 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Benitez, Margarita, Undated; nam_ua950.003-167 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- But, Benjamin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-168 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Bennett, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-169 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Benson, Gregory, Undated; nam_ua950.003-170 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Benson-Wright, Penelope, Undated; nam_ua950.003-171 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Berenguer, A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-172 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Berg, Lawrence K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-173 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Bergau, Nancy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-174 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Berger, Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-175 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Berger, Morris I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-176 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Berger, Morris I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-177 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Berger, Ron, Undated; nam_ua950.003-178 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Berger, Sheila, Undated; nam_ua950.003-179 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Berger, Sheila, Undated; nam_ua950.003-180 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Bergeson, Clarance O., Undated; nam_ua950.003-181 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Bergin, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-182 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Berkowitz, Joel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-183 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Berkun, Howard, 1969 April 24; nam_ua950.003-184 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Berman, Jeffrey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-185 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Bernier, Joseph Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-186 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Bernstein, Roberta, Undated; nam_ua950.003-187 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Berry, Leonard J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-188 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Bers, Melvin K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-189 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Bessette, Tom, Undated; nam_ua950.003-190 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Bethea, Mahaliel "J.R.", Undated; nam_ua950.003-191 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Bettelheim, Bruno, Undated; nam_ua950.003-192 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Betz, Margaret, 1959; nam_ua950.003-193 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Biggs, Donald A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-194 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Bingham, Sarah M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-195 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Birchenough, Harry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-196 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Birckbichler, Diane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-197 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Birge, Scott R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-198 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Birkhead, Guthrie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-199 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Birkland, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-200 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Birn, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-201 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Birr, Kendall A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-202 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Bjarnason, Thor, Undated; nam_ua950.003-203 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Black, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-204 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Blair, Mary Grace, Undated; nam_ua950.003-205 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Blais, Archie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-206 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Blaisdell, Kenneth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-207 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Blanchard, Duncan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-208 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Blanchard, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-209 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Blanton, Hart, Undated; nam_ua950.003-210 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Blatner, Barbara A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-211 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Blau, Judith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-212 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Blau, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-213 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Bleiberg, German, Undated; nam_ua950.003-214 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Bleichert, Henry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-215 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Blotcher, Donald H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-216 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Block Eric, Undated; nam_ua950.003-217 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Blodgett, Hollis F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-218 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Blodgett, Royann S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-219 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Blood, Susan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-220 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bloniarz, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-221 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Blount, Stanley, Undated; nam_ua950.003-222 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Blue, Leonard A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-223 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Blum, Mark L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-224 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Blum, Terry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-225 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Blumenthal, Joel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-226 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Boahm, Anne E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-227 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Bockhorst, Diane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-228 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Boehm, Thomas Allen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-229 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Boice, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-230 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Bolce, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-231 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Boll, Jennifer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-232 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Bonk, Sharon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-233 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Boomsliter, Paul C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-234 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Boomsliter, Paul C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-235 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Boomsliter, Paul C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-236 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Bonawitz, Irving M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-237 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Bond, Dorcas, 1970 March 7; nam_ua950.003-238 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Bonnor, Florence, Undated; nam_ua950.003-239 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Bonventre, Vincent, Undated; nam_ua950.003-240 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Boots, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-241 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Bord, Nancy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-242 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Borys, Ted, Undated; nam_ua950.003-243 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Bosart, Lance F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-244 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Bosco, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-245 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Bouchard, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-246 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Bouchard, Christine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-247 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Bowles, Brett, Undated; nam_ua950.003-248 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Bowen, John H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-249 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Bowman, Charles L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-250 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Bowman, Joseph Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-251 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Boyd, Kathryn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-252 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Boyer, Ernest L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-253 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Boyer, Ernest L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-254 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Bradbury, John L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-255 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Bradish, Gaynor F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-256 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Bradt, Douglass, Undated; nam_ua950.003-257 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Brady, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-258 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Braithwaite, Bernard S., 1963 Summer; nam_ua950.003-259 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Brannon, Lillian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-260 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Bravos, Theodore, 1973; nam_ua950.003-261 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Bray, William G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-262 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Bredderman, Theodore, 1986; nam_ua950.003-263 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Breen, Joan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-264 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Breitbart, Yuri, Undated; nam_ua950.003-265 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Brewer, George E., 1964; nam_ua950.003-266 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Brewer, Floyd Irving, Undated; nam_ua950.003-267 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Briand, Kevin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-268 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Briar-Lawson, Katharine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-269 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Brickman, Leonard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-270 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Brickman, Louis, 1967; nam_ua950.003-271 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Brickman, Louis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-272 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Briere, Jean-Francois, Undated; nam_ua950.003-273 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Briere, Eloise, Undated; nam_ua950.003-274 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Briggs, Robert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-275 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Brigham, Bill, Undated; nam_ua950.003-276 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Brigham, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-277 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Brighton, Deborah, Undated; nam_ua950.003-278 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Brinberg, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-279 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Brink, Harold, Undated; nam_ua950.003-280 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Brinster, Russell, Undated; nam_ua950.003-281 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Brisley, Kathy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-282 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Broadwell, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-283 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Bromley, Ray, Undated; nam_ua950.003-284 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Bronson, Barnard S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-285 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Brooker, George W. Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-286 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Brown, Ian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-287 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Brough, Jane N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-288 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Brown, Clifford W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-289 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Brown, Craig M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-290 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Brown, Herbert I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-291 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Brown, Herbert I., 1967; nam_ua950.003-292 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Brown, Jerram L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-293 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Brown, Jerram L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-294 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Brown, Karen E.K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-295 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Brown, Lester B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-296 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Brown, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-297 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Brown, Neil C. Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-298 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Brown, Neil, Undated; nam_ua950.003-299 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- Brown, Peter G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-300 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Brown, Shai, Undated; nam_ua950.003-301 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- Brown, Shirley, Undated; nam_ua950.003-302 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Brown, W.J. (Langdon), Undated; nam_ua950.003-303 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Brown, William J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-304 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Brown, William P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-305 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Brown, William P., 1966; nam_ua950.003-306 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Brown, William P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-307 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Brown, William P., 1971; nam_ua950.003-308 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Brown, William P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-309 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Brown, William P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-310 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Brownlow, Winston, Undated; nam_ua950.003-311 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Brownstein, Alex, Undated; nam_ua950.003-312 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Brubacher, Abram R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-313 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Bruch, Monroe A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-314 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Bruce, Lura, Undated; nam_ua950.003-315 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Brucker, Denise, Undated; nam_ua950.003-316 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Brunelli, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-317 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Brustman, Mary Jane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-318 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Brustman, Mary Jane J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-319 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Brustman, Mary Jane, 1983; nam_ua950.003-320 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Bryan, Ashley M., 1961; nam_ua950.003-321 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Bryant, Bonita, 1981-2000; nam_ua950.003-322 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Bryant, Bonita I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-323 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bucchigrossi, Patricia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-324 (Box 5, Folder 14)